Okay, everyone's seen a horse do this.
Pblpblpblpbl!
We don't know what it means,
we just know that horses
always say-- pblpblpblpbl!
Pretty interesting, right?
But it's even more
interesting in slow motion.
So, let's take a look at Sam and
me from earlier today going--
pblpblpblpbl!
But all slow-mo-ified.
Go, Freddie.
Playback ready.
Okay, first me.
And now me.
And now both of us.
And now Freddie.
And Spencer.
And last but not least my crazy
grandmother who we call--
she's actually half horse!
Okay, next on the iCarly--
--Sam and I are gonna show you
one of the funniest guys on the Web.
Even funnier than the burping giraffe.
His name is Fred, Fred is awesome.
He makes these insanely
hilarious videos that are
sorta impossible to describe.
So we'll shut up and you just watch.
All right, people.
We give you-- hey, it's Fred,
and it's really nice out,
so I think I'm gonna
go swimming later.
My mom found this really
cool pool at the dump.
It's really big and really deep.
I think I might drown.
I also got a letter in the mail.
It might be from my dad.
"To Fred--"
what the heck is this?
"Ha ha. You probably thought
"this was your dad, you loser.
"Anyways, I told you "that
I know where you live.
P.S. Your voice is weird."
So the crazy guy really
does know where I live.
What if he comes over here
and steals all the food
out of our fridge?
while I'm going swimming it's
because I'm uncomfortable
with my body.
1, 2, 3.
Oh, my God! There's a shark!
This pool is small.
Oh, my God.
Kevin's chasing after me.
Okay, well, since I'm really mad,
I think I'm gonna go because
I don't think I wanna take
all my anger out on you.
Bye.
Okay, I say that video
deserves a-- [Applause]
Yeah, all right.
Okay, next on iCarly, Sam
and I, we're gonna shave
some stuffed animals.
Which is always a good time.
But now I'm thinking that
instead we should watch
another Fred video.
What you think, Sam?
I think we should.
Freddie?
I think you guys should
shave the stuffed animals.
You don't wanna see
another Fred video?
Not really.
Why not, fudge face?
Because I don't think
Fred is all that funny.
Uh, do you know how
popular his videos are?
Each one gets like a billion views.
How can you not think
Fred is not funny?
I didn't say he was unfunny.
I just don't love his videos.
Well, apparently Freddie's got
his little anti-bacterial
underpants in a bunch.
I stopped wearing
antibacterial underpants
and I'm entitled to my opinion.
And it's my opinion that
we're out of time anyway.
So till the next
iCarly-- stay in school.
Recycle.
Pour milk on your parents.
Hug a duck.
Eat a stick of butter.
And shampoo a squirrel.
Bye.
See ya on the next iCarly.
Ciao.
Peace.
And we're clear.
Yeah.
Whoo!
You guys done with the show?
Uh-huh.
Yup.
Just finished.
Cool, check out what I found.
What is that?
Looks like something my
aunt Maggie would cough up.
Well, she's a smoker.
What is it?
It's my magic meatball.
I carried this thing around with me
like all during seventh grade,
which was arguably the best year
of my life.
What does a magic meatball do?
It gives you perfect advice.
You ask it any yes or no question,
shake it and then, boom,
it tells you what to do.
That's so stupid.
It is not.
I read an article about a
guy who made $3 million
using one of these to pick stocks.
Dude, it's a toy.
A magic toy.
Here. Watch.
Will my phone ring in
the next five seconds?
The answer is no.
Spooky, huh?
In 5, 4, 3, 2-- [Music]
I know, you see
somehow the world
will change for me
and be so wonderful
live life, breathe air
I know somehow
we're gonna get there
and feel so wonderful
it's all for real
I'm telling you
just how I feel
so wake up the members
of my nation
it's your time to be
there's no chance
unless you take one
every time you see
the brighter side
of every situation
some things are meant to be
so give it your best
[music]
Should I drink a glass
of this iced tea?
Negative.
Aww.
Wahoo punch?
The meatball says no.
Aww.
That's all we have.
What am I supposed to drink?
Ketchup?
The answer is yes.
Well, you haven't steered me
wrong yet, magic meatball.
[Knock on door]
Hey.
Wh-when did you-- what
are you doing here?
I was in the neighborhood,
wanted food,
didn't wanna to pay for it.
Here I am.
All right.
Hey. Carly home yet?
No, but everyone else is.
Why are you drinking ketchup?
My magic meatball told me to.
I'm tired.
I'm gonna go take a nap.
Hey, do you know what's going on?
I've gotten about 10 texts in
the last 5 minutes telling me
to check out splashface.
Yeah, Carly just texted
me saying the same thing.
She says to look
up "Fred is dead."
Huh. "Fred is dead."
Here it is, just posted an hour ago.
Click on it.
Hey. It's me.
If you saw the last iCarly,
then you heard Freddie Benson
say he doesn't like my Fred
videos-- 'cause I don't think Fred
is all that funny.
Well, thank you for
crushing my feelings.
Now I'm not gonna post any
more Fred videos ever again.
Internet, I click you goodbye.
You see what you did?
You killed Fred.
Aah!
I just gave my honest opinion.
Hey, you guys gonna be okay here
alone till Carly gets back?
Sure.
Why?
I thought you were tired.
Yeah. But my meatball
says I wanna go surfing.
[Music]
Oh.
I see you girls are fans of Fred.
Heh.
Oh, dear. Guys, guys.
Unh! Augh! Aah!
Yeah, thank you.
Boo.
Oh, come on, guys, it's not my fault.
Aah.
All right, who threw this at my head?
Who threw this low-fat fat
cake at my head? Huh?
Well, I'm keeping it.
Yaah.
What's up, guys?
We just had an emergency
meeting of the mathletes.
Oh, well, how come I wasn't invited?
'Cause you killed Fred.
All I did was give my opinion.
Well, your opinion stinks.
Easy, Shawn.
I'm very sorry to say this,
but the mathletes are
subtracting you from the team.
What?
Come on, I'm our best long divider.
Then you should be able to
handle this long division--
--between us and you.
[Sighs]
Oww!
Hey, Benson, this Fred thing
is getting way outta control.
Kids keep booing and
throwing things stuff at us.
Get up!
You just had to trash talk Fred.
I didn't trash talk him.
It's not Freddie's fault.
He just gave his opinion.
Yeah. And anyway it's not
like-- [Kids laughing]
Uh-oh, check it out.
Augh! Why are they
blaming our whole show?
It's all Freddie's fault.
Hey!
Well-- well, it's way worse
for me, I've been kicked out
of everything except the
junior bow and arrow club.
I'm out.
--Because I just don't see
what's funny about Fred.
It's not my fault he quit.
Hey, you don't have to call me names.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you're a bigger one.
Who was that?
My aunt Jennifer.
Who texted you?
Gibby.
He wants us to check out
some website called
neverwatchicarly. com.
Well, that can't be good.
I know it can't be good.
Freddie.
Already on it.
neverwatchicarly. com.
Oh, man.
Some guy started a whole website
just to try to stop people
from watching iCarly?
All 'cause you irritated Fred.
Aaaah! Oww. Ah.
Okay, let's not panic.
How many people have
signed up to support him?
Um, a few hundred.
Okay. That's not so many.
Wait.
I just refreshed the page.
Now it's up to 3,000.
How many?
Refreshing.
Yikes, 18,000.
Are you sure?
Refreshing. 90-- okay, why
don't we stop refreshing. Unh!
[Elevator bell dings]
Uh, what you got there?
It's a smoothie.
I think she meant the gigantic bird.
Oh! This is Marvin.
He's an ostrich.
I just bought him.
Your magic meatball told you to?
Yes.
[Doorbell rings]
Hey, would you get that?
Marvin wants a root beer.
We're gonna go into the kitchen.
Carly, any comment on the Fred fight?
What? It's not a fight.
But iCarly killed Fred.
Don't you feel guilty?
No. Freddie was just
expressing his opinion.
Do you agree with his opinion?
Yeah, do you also think the
Fred videos are terrible?
I never said the Fred
videos are terrible.
Sam, is it true that you've
been arrested four times?
Three times.
Get your facts right.
And get outta here.
Arrrgh, Marvin bit my pants.
No, Freddie was just
expressing his opinion.
You agree with Freddie's opinion?
Get outta here.
This whole thing is getting insane.
Did you check and see if the
Fred guy answered your e-mail?
I check every 10 minutes.
What won't he write back?
Because he's a jerk.
You're the queen of the jerks.
Why pick on me?
Two reasons.
Number one, I love it.
Number two, this whole fight
between iCarly and Fred
is your fault.
I just said I didn't think his
videos were all that funny.
He's the one who overreacted and
started this whole brouhaha.
Brouhaha.
You can't say things like
brouhaha and not expect
people to hit you.
[E-mail beeps]
Fred wrote back.
He did?
What did he say?
Uh-- will he start making
the Fred videos again?
No, but he says he'll meet
with us and talk about it.
He wants us to go to his house.
Where does he live?
Shelby, Idaho.
That's about 4 hours from here.
My mom could drive us.
She got her license back?
I didn't say that.
Well, did she get her van
back from the police?
Maybe someone else should drive us.
This is going to be a very
important art exhibit
that will feature the most promising
young artists in Seattle,
and we'd really like to include
some of your sculptures.
Wow! That is such an
honor for you to ask me.
So you'll do it?
Could you excuse me
for just one second?
Of course.
Okay, magic meatball.
Should I let him use my
sculptures in his art exhibit?
Definitely not.
Oh, please.
This is such a huge opportunity.
Ask again later.
But we need to discuss this now.
I must advise against it.
Come on!
I drank ketchup, I bought an ostrich.
I did everything you told me to.
Help me out this one time.
The answer is no.
That's it!
You're not magic.
You're just a mean meatball.
Oh! I'm sorry.
I was just arguing with my meatball.
Marvin, get back in your room.
Is that an ostrich?
Yeah. He's friendly-- when
he's not biting my pants.
I see.
Well, about your sculpture-- mm-hmm.
I think we should-- wait!
Mr. Feldon, come on.
I know it seems--Aargh!
Hey, will you drive us somewhere?
Sure. Where?
Shelby, Idaho.
Mm, okay.
Marvin, I'm going to Idaho.
Stay off of the Internet.
Hello! We're here.
It's Carly, Sam and Freddie.
Okay. This is the coolest
treehouse in the universe.
Yeah.
It's nicer than where I live.
Whoa!
Check out this editing setup.
Don't touch it.
Hey!
Hi!
You're here.
Hey! Hey!
How cool is this treehouse!
You know when I was a kid, I
wanted to build one like this,
but dad always said they--aah!
I'll wait down here.
Who was that?
Skip it.
Yeah.
Look, Freddie is really sorry
that he hurt your feelings.
Yeah, I'd like to hear that from
the guy in the Bumblebee shirt.
Hello!
I'm sorry that I hurt your feelings.
I didn't mean to.
Okay. I forgive you.
You do?
Nope.
What?
Say you think my videos are funny.
No.
Come on.
Freddie!
We're in a treehouse
in Idaho, just say it.
Why should I say it?
Let me talk to the boy.
Sam.
Can I use this?
Please.
Sam, no. Get away from me.
Aw! Ooh, not that! Ooh, ow!
Oh, good gravy! Oh! Oh, no!
Your videos are hilarious.
Aagh! I don't know
what I was thinking
when I said I didn't get him.
What's not to get?
Aagh! You're a comedy wizard.
Well?
Are we cool?
He's chuckling.
I see him chuckling.
Why are you chuckling?
'Cause you guys are cute.
We're cute?
Yeah.
I was never mad.
I love iCarly.
But you said that Freddie
hurt your feelings.
And that's why you stopped
making your Fred videos.
Come on.
I'm not gonna stop
making the Fred videos.
Okay. I get it.
The real problem here is
that you're insane am I?
Uh, pretty much, yeah.
Kind of psycho.
Yep.
Guys, since this war between
iCarly and me started,
do you realize my Fred videos
have gotten like 10 times
more popular than they already were?
So you did all this for publicity?
Totally.
Just to make your Fred
videos more popular?
Not just the Fred videos, iCarly too.
What are you talking--
when was the last time
that you guys checked
your website ratings?
Uh, I don't know,
like a few weeks ago.
Well, check them now.
See? Web traffic to iCarly.
Com is higher than it's ever been.
People love a good fight.
Ooh, that's terrible.
I mean, it was brilliant
in a terrible way.
It was terribly brilliant, okay?
Hey, there's something huge down
there trying to kill me. Aah!
It's either a large dog
or a small bear. Aah!
That's my dog Tibbals.
Tibbals has my foot. Aah!
Will you guys go make sure he's okay?
I'm not going down.
Come on.
Ow, ow! I'm coming. Aah!
Oh! Ow!
You know, you could have at least
told us what you were doing.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
So are we friends?
I guess.
You sure?
Sure.
Should we kiss?
No.
In 5, 4, 3, 2-- me llamo Carly!
Me llamo Sam!
And this is iCarly.
The only show on the Internet
that fights global warming--
--and prevents pimples.
Now, a lot of you guys have
been following the fight
that's been going on
between us and Fred.
Yeah, well, guess what.
The fight is over!
Over.
Yeah, baby.
And to prove it-- --say hello
to our new best friend--
--the genius behind Fred.
Yeah!
Whoo!
Okay, Freddie, switch to the b-cam.
Come out here and show the love.
Switching to b-cam.
See, we made up.
We're all good.
Oh, come on, you guys can
do better than that.
Hug! Hug!
Hug! Hug! Hug! Hug!
Hug! Hug! Hug!
All right, all right.
Okay, just to prove that we're
all buds now-- --check out
this brand-new video.
Watch it.
Do it.
Playback.
Hey, it's Fred.
Look at my cabbage.
Why can't it speak Spanish?
Muchacho.
My stomach feels queasy.
Shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
Have you seen my cabbage?
Oh, my gosh, a person.
Why did Fred flee?
People scare me. Aah.
This ostrich thinks I'm a lady.
I wanna go to cranberry parade.
I buried Paul.
More people. Aah!
I'm eating chips with trans-fats.
Oh, my God, I'm so happy.
I'm hiding under a Toyota.
It's a sports utility vehicle.
The cabbage. Aah!
Me and the ostrich
are getting married.
Aah!
We're wearing matching ties.
I'm running.
Who invented marshmallows?
What's wrong with David Schwimmer?
I like to sniff cheese.
Cheese!
My mother ate my turtle.
My bathroom is purple.
How do you like me now, junior?
Is Kevin still better than me?
I'm pretty sure I'm way
better than Kevin now.
Who wants to swim in my pool?
Swimming! Swimming!
Swimming! Swimming! Ah!
I'm not gonna take off my shirt.
No!
I'm swimming.
I bet you Kevin's so
jealous right now.
Jealous.
What if these noodles
are Kevin's intestines?
That'd make me so happy.
My friends are here.
We're swimming with noodles.
My shorts are too tight.
It's like a community bath.
Cabbages cabbages.
Cabbages.
Aaaaaaaah!
This pool is so tiny. Bye!
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0